frymulti.com 2010-12-30

# Fry, Inc. - Privacy Policy

**At Fry, Inc., We take your privacy seriously. This statement describes the privacy policy for the entire Web site, including what information we capture and how we use it. By "the entire Web site" we mean the domain fry.com.**

##### Information Collection and Use

Fry captures information from its visitors in two different ways, directly (through information you submit to us) and indirectly (through our site technology).

##### Log Files

Our site collects traffic information from visitors to be used for statistical analysis and Web site improvement. When you access our site, we collect information about your visit in a log file on the server. Log file information may include, but is not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We do not try to track you or to identify you individually, but we do review this information to understand overall trends and to determine what kinds of content are popular and useful to our visitors.

We may also use tracking and analysis software and services provided by NetIQ Corporation to identify and analyze patterns of browsing by our visitors. We use this information to understand which parts of the site seem to be interesting, whether any aspects of the site seem to be confusing or overlooked, and how well our marketing activities are working.

##### Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files of information that Web sites can store on your computer’s hard drive. The Fry site assigns a unique number-letter combination that is used only when you are on our site. This number-letter combination is used to identify and analyze patterns of browsing by our visitors. No personal information is stored in this cookie or gathered from any other files that you have on your computer.

##### Email Sent to Us

Throughout our site, we have email addresses posted to encourage our users to contact us directly with inquiries or feedback. If a user submits an email to us, we respond to the email directly to answer questions or comments. We do not sell or otherwise disclose email addresses to third parties.

##### Links and Information Gathered by Others 

Our site contains links to other sites. Fry does not operate these sites, cannot control what information such sites gather or what such sites do with the information, and is therefore not responsible for the activities of the operators of such sites. This privacy statement only applies to information collected by Fry, Inc.

##### Changes to the Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our homepage, and/or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. However, if we plan to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify such users by email if, and to the extent that, such users have provided their email addresses to us. If you do not reply to such an email, or we receive a reply of "undeliverable" or a similar message from your last known email address, in either case after a reasonable time, we will use the information in the different manner. Exceptions We may collect personally identifiable information and use such information if we are required to do so by law or if we deem it advisable in the course of assisting law enforcement activities or protecting our Web site(s) and other information.

##### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or need to contact us, please use the following contact information:

**Privacy Liaison**  
Fry, Inc.   
650 Avis Drive   
Ann Arbor, Michigan 48108   
email: webmaster@fry.com   
Telephone: (734) 741-0640
